

# Contact

Located in Vila Nova de Gaia, Porto - PT +351 936 052 219 joaovictorc2506@gmail.com <u>LinkedIn</u>

# Skills

- Portuguese fluent
- English B2
- Microsoft Office Suite
- Web Developer

# Education

Estácio de Sá University -UNESA

Bachelor's degree in Information Systems

Completed in 2023

# JOÃO VICTOR CASTRO DA CONCEIÇÃO

## POWER BI | SUPPORT | WEB DEVELOPER | JAVASCRIPT | PYTHON

### SUMMARY

I'm a passionate professional in creating impactful and functional digital experiences. With begginer level Python and a strong skill set in web development, including advanced knowledge in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, and SQL. Having experience in two previous positions as a web programmer. I am currently eligible to work on Portugal and Brazil, with proficiency in English at a B2 level and C2 Portuguese.

I am excited to contribute my experience in an international environment. In addition to my skills, I have mastery over the Microsoft Office Suite, providing a comprehensive and effective approach to projects.

### **EXPERIENCE**

# DESENVOLVEDOR FULL STACK E-COMMERCE | PRESENCA DE LUXO-PT 10/2024-TODAY

- Responsible for the development of systems for the financial, HR, and administrative sectors.
- Investigation and problem-solving in a team, using agile methodologies.
- Conducting tests and continuous improvements to ensure the usability and performance of the systems.
- Assisting in the construction of web pages.
- Use of JavaScript extensions and interaction with databases.
- Creation and management of prestashop modules.

# TRAINEE TI|NTL NOVA TECNOLOGIA LTDA - BR 02/2021-07/2022

- System Development (for financial, HR and administrative sectors)
- Problem investigation and solution creation alongside the team in an agile manner.
- Testing and continuous improvement of usability and performance.
- Report elaboration.
- Supporting in page building.
- Working with JavaScript extensions and databases.

### PROGRAMMER | RASV LIMITED - BR 12/2020-01/2021

- Perform maintenance on existing software.
- Participate in meetings with leadership.
- Alignment and update of daily activities with squads.
- Contribute to project execution.
- Develop queries for SQL Server and MySQL databases.
- Interpret projects and needs with a systemic vision.
- Develop, execute, and implement web system projects using programming languages, within appropriate standards of quality, efficiency, and security.